Kiumars Khaleghi

Summary

I studied **computer software engineering** at Shahid Chamran Kerman Technical and vocational university with 2+ years of work experience. I used to repair Electrical and Electronic devices. Also, I've some experience in creating simple software modules for embedded devices. My goal is to design and optimize embedded systems and IoT devices on both Hardware and Software sides.

I'm trying to research and learn more about IoT device technologies, so at this time, I'm learning PCB manufacturing and debugging electronic devices in Parmoon company.

Experience

Embedded systems Engineer – IoT Intern - 02/2021 to present Payesh Gostar Parmoon, Kerman

- PCB manufacturing process
- PCB debugging and analysis
- Embedded system software developing
- Embedded system monitoring

Electronic Repair Technician - 09/2018 to 02/2020 **Novin Electronic,** Kerman

- Repairing electronic mobile devices
- PCB manufacturing process
- PCB debugging and analysis
- Customer Services and Support
- Finding new solutions for software module challenges

Cisco CCNA Network Intern - 09/2017 to 11/2017 **Kerman Informatics,** Kerman

- Simulating Network topologies
- Network designing and repairing
- Configuring Cisco and Mikrotik Network Devices

Education

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering - 2021

Shahid Chamran Kerman Technical and vocational university



Contact

+98 (921) 534-4275 <u>qxaxel@gmail.com</u> www.linkedin.com/in/qkhaleghi

Highlights

- Embedded systems- IoT
- R&D
- Cisco CCNA
- Python and C
- Repair Technician
- GNU Linux
- Friendly